

obada hallak

Full stack developer

I am a BAIT in Syrian Virtual University student, and I have experience with Laravel and Vuejs (three years with Laravel, one year with Vueis), I hardworking programmer with a flair for creating elegant solutions in the least amount of time with many programming and developing skills.

obadahalak538@gmail.com



+963954012804



🤗 medan, Syria, Damascus



github.com/obadahalak

WORK EXPERIENCE

backend-developer (laravel) freelancer

2021 - Present mid-leven

Frontend developer (VueJs) freelancer

2023 - Present iunior

Penetration tester

junior

EDUCATION

BAIT

Syrian Virtual University SVU

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Book store (laravel) (2023)

- A Book store web application that provides services to readers and authors such as showing books according to the categories preferred by the user, tracking down his activities and organizing user's schedule to help him set up a plan to complete reading a book
- GitHub obadahalak/bookstore at master

Techmedic (2023)

- Techmedic is a trading company specialized in Medical supplies, The frontend was coded by me using Vuejs
- Techmedic (techmedicco.com)
- obadahalak/techmedic (github.com)
- obadahalak/techmedic-admin (github.com)

IFMIS-app (2022)

- A sports application that provides services to athletes and visitors for free, The backend was coded by me
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=dev.ifmis.news

COURSES, CERTIFICATIONS

Winner of the third stage of the CYBER CTF competition (10/2020)

National AGENCY FOR NETWORK SERVICE

1st place in Syria National Cybersecurity CTF (09/2021)

CYBER TALENTS

CEH V10 (09/2021)

Syrian Virtual University SVU

Java Course

Hadara-Center

Oracle Database 11g: SQL Fundamentals (05/2019)

NewHorizons

C# Course (02/2019 - 04/2019)

Hadara-Center